基本上没有什么事
There's pretty much nothing that.
是Winchester兄弟解决不了的
The Winchesters can't do.
如果他们在一起的话
If they work together.
我找到如何关上地狱之门的方法了
I figured out how to close the Gates of Hell.
天堂需要你的帮助 Castiel
Heaven needs your help,Castiel.
你好啊 Castiel
Hello,Castiel.
我值得
I deserve.
被爱
To be loved.
Sammy 快停下
Sammy,stop.
放手吧
Just let it go.
Sam
Sam.
怎么回事
What's happening.
天使
Angels.
在坠落
They're falling.
这一点儿都说不通啊
This makes no sense.
到底落下来了多少天使
I mean,how many angels fell.
几百个 几千个
Hundreds?Thousands.
但是根本没人看见
And nobody sees anything.
这真是
This is.
看
Look at this.
媒体报道说是流星雨 他们是认真的吗
They're calling it a meteor shower,seriously.
有什么不对劲吗 你还好吗
What's going on man?Are you okay.
问我吗
Me.
嗯 我只是
Yeah,I just.
- 我还好 只是 - 只是现在咱们手上
- Fine,just - It's just we got.
多了这个奇葩的大难题
A major freaking crap that's on our hands.
多谢提醒了
Yeah,you gotta tell me about that.
上千个超能力混蛋们坠天
Thousands of superpower dicks touching down and.
我们却不知道从何下手
We got no idea where to start.
天使不是我们该关心的
Angels are not our problem right now.
好吗 或者是恶魔
Okay,or demons.
或者Metatron 再或者Cass到底怎么了
Or Metatron,or whatever the hell happened to Cass.
为什么 就因为咱俩
Why?Because we.
在那栋教堂里来了个热情拥抱
Hugged it out in that church and.
现在我们要去迪士尼玩儿了吗
And now we're gonna go to Disneyland.
Dean 你自己说的
Dean you said yourself.
事情没解决前 不能休息
We're not gonna sleep until this is done.
我知道
I know.
- 到底怎么了 - 是你
- So what's the problem? - You.
听着 现在的情况就是这么糟
Look,there's no easy way to say this,okay.
但是当时发生了什么事
But something happened back there.
在那栋教堂里
In the church.
我不知道是什么 我也不知道为什么
I don't know what.I don't know why.
Sam 你快死了
You're dying,Sam.
你够了
Shut up.
全球范围流星雨
GLOBAL METEOR SHOWER.
核磁共振显示他体内有大面积烧伤
The MRI shows the massive internal.
已经感染到重要器官
Burns affecting many of the major organs.
大脑严重供氧不足
Oxygen to the brain has been severely deprived.
昏迷是因为身体的生理反应
The coma is the result of the body.
保证一切消耗最小化
Doing everything in its limited power.
这样能避免更多的伤害
To protect itself from further harm.
不应该是这个样子的
This wasn't supposed to happen.
如果你弟弟继续维持这种状态
If your brother continues on this trajectory.
这些机器是能让他活着 但是
The machines might keep him alive,but.
终究还是会死
He'll be dead.
从技术角度讲 是的
Technically,yes.
恐怕真是如此
I'm afraid so.
也就是说 他不会恢复
So,there's no recovering.
我是说 不会痊愈
I mean there's no bouncing back.
什么都不会发生
There's no nothing.
恐怕现在要听天由命了
I'm afraid that's in God's hands now.
你是医生
You're a doctor.
你身为一个专业的医生
You're a medical professional.
但是你告诉我
You're trying to tell me.
我弟弟 该听天由命吗
That my brother's life is in God's hand.
这算什么 安慰我吗
What,is that supposed to be a comfort.
Dougherty先生
Mr.Dougherty.
老天爷跟此没有关系
God has nothing to do in this equation.
- 完全没有 - 我不是说
- At all - I didn't mean.
别扯听天由命
That's not good enough.
礼拜堂
Chapel.
Cass 你在吗
Cass,are you there.
Sammy受伤了
Sammy's hurt.
他
He's hurt.
他伤得很严重
He's hurt pretty bad.
还有
And.
我知道你觉得我生你气了
I know you think that I'm pissed at you.
但是我不在乎天使的坠落
Okay,but I don't care the angels fell.
所以 不管你做了什么
So,whatever you did.
或者没做什么
Or didn't do.
都没关系
It doesn't matter.
我们会解决的
Okay,we'll work it out.
求你了 我需要你
Please,man,I need you here.
不管了
Screw it.
好吧 听着
Okay,listen up.
这条祷告面向所有
This one goes out to any angel.
能听到的天使
With their ears on.
我是Dean Winchester
This is Dean Winchester.
我需要帮助
And I need your help.
我是Dean Winchester
This is Dean Winchester.
我需要帮助
And I need your help.
是这样 我们在林伍德纪念医院
The deal is this,Linwood Memorial Hospital.
伦道夫 纽约
Randolph,New York.
第一个来帮助我的人
The first one who could help me.
就能得到我的帮助作为回报 你们知道
Gets my help in return,and you know that.
我可是块宝
Ain't nothing.
亲爱的
Honey.
大家心里都清楚 我跟你们立场不一致
Hell,it's no secret that we haven't always seen eye to eye.
但你们也知道我是个信守承诺的人
But you know that I'm good for my word.
还有
And.
一般我是不会轻易开口向你们求助的
It wouldn't be asking if I wasn't needing.
所以
So.
说你快死了并不代表
Just because you're dying doesn't mean.
你已经死了 你还活着好吗
You're dead.Not yet,okay.
咱们已经度过了最艰难的时期
We've jimmied ourselves out of worse.
这次我们会挺过去的
We're gonna fight this.
我来想办法 你坚持住就行
I got the plan,you just got to hang on.
听到了吗
You hear me.
听到了
Absolutely.
- 你觉得我骗你 - 差不多
- You think I'm lying - Pretty much.
嗯
Yeah.
那你知不知道 我们现在
Do you understand that we're not.
根本就不是真的坐在车里
Really in this car right now.
我们在你脑子里
We're in your head.
你还在昏迷着 而且就要死了
And you're in a coma and are dying.
- 你怎么知道 - 因为我就是你
- How do you know that - Because I'm you.
你也是你 一切的一切
And you're you,all of this.
都是你
Is you.
我们在你的脑子里
We're in your head.
你是认真的吗
You're serious.
我放弃试炼的真正原因仅仅是
The whole reason I stopped doing the trials.
我还不想死
Was not to die.
等咱们下次碰见Naomi
And the next time we see Naomi.
Metatron或者其他那些个幕后黑手
Or Metatron or whomever's to blame for this.
我们会讨个公道的 但是现在
We'll get some justice,but for right now.
咱们得帮你挺过这一关
We got to fight this man.
好吧
Okay.
有什么计划吗
All right,what's the plan.
我还在想
I'm working on it.
什么意思
What does that mean.
我显然是 快死了
I...I'm kinda dying here,apparently.
意思就是我会想出办法的 行吗
It means I'm working on it,all right.
问题是
The thing is.
如果我快死了 我信你 真的
If I'm dying and,I believe you,I do.
但是你作为你自己 事实上确实我的一部分
But if you're you,but you're really me.
你是我有着求生欲望的那一部分
And you're the part of me that wants to fight to live.
对
Yes.
虽然不知道你在讲什么 但是请继续
I have no idea what you just said but continue.
但如果
But if.
你都不知道
You don't have any idea.
怎么帮我解决困难
How I'm supposed to fight.
那不是就说明
Then that might supposed to be.
本来这件事儿就没希望了吗
No fighting at all.
你是认真的吗
Are you serious.
废话 当然是
Hell yes,he's serious.
要我说
I mean if you ask me.
他说的全都在点儿上
I think the kid's got a good point.
嘿 老兄
Hey,buddy.
你没事儿吧
You okay.
会痛
It hurts.
你刚才在
What the hell you're doing.
马路中间干什么呢
In the middle of the road like that.
我能听见天使的声音
I heard angels.
要不我给你拿点儿水来
How about we get you some water.
我
I.
我不喝水
I don't drink water.
在海拔这么高的地方脱水很折磨人的 先生
Dehydration is a real bitch up here,mister.
手机
A phone.
你有手机吗
Do you have a phone.
海拔太高了 没有信号
No signal up here.
要不载你一程
How about a lift.
是的 没错
Yes,good.
我一般都是用飞的 但是我
I would fly but I.
我现在没有翅膀了
I have no wings.
没有了
Not anymore.
好吧
Right.
Sam说他想去死 你还觉得他说得对
Sam wants to die and you think he's got a point.
我还不想死 行了吧
Okay,I don't want to die.
我只是想问 万一我本来就应该死呢
I asked if maybe I was supposed to die.
闭嘴 Sam
Shut up,Sam.
你 快消失
You,go.
在你开始说我坏话之前
And before you throw me under the bus.
不用感谢我去地狱救人那档子事儿
You're welcomed for the Hell rescue.
嘿 首先
Hey,first of all.
人不是你救的 白痴 是Sam
You didn't rescue jack,half-wit.Sam did.
其次
Second of all.
Sam 你还在昏迷中
Sam,you're in a coma.
像现在这种破情况
Now,suck as that may.
说不定放手就是最好的方法
Sometimes that's just the way things go.
你在说什么鬼 总会有办法的
What're you talking about!There's always a way.
这是你教我们的
You taught us that.
你是说像你俩中的某人一样
You mean like the way one of you idjits.
冲动莽撞的自以为能骗过死神
Does some bass-ackwards crazy thing to beat death.
比如 出卖自己的灵魂
Like sold your soul.
没错 出卖我的灵魂
Exactly like selling my soul.
说的就跟你那么做有什么好结果一样
Yeah,like that worked so well the last time.
够了 你们俩 我都无法集中精力思考了
Enough!Both of you!I can't hear myself think.
等等 你不会觉得他是对的吧
Well,you're not actually buying this,are you.
不好意思 请问你死了吗
Excuse me,are you dead.
我才是不喘气的那个
Because I am.
说不定我在这儿是因为
And maybe I'm here because I'm the part of Sam.
我才是Sam现在最需要的那一部分
That actually knows what the hell he's talking about.
我才是坐在前排的人
I'm in the front seat.
Sam让我坐在这儿因为他想活下去
Because Sam put me here because he wants to fight.
没错吧
Right.
好吧
Well.
还真不怎么舒服
That just got really uncomfortable.
回见 Dean
See you,Dean.
Sam 你要是敢
Sam,don't you dare.
啧啧啧 我是对的吧
Yip,yip,yip.Am I right.
说实话 Bobby 我
Honestly Bobby I.
我不知道什么是正确的了
I don't know what's right.
先走走
Let's walk.
嘿
Hey.
不 我不能拿你的钱的
No,I can't take your money.
买个手机 或者三明治
For the phone,and a sandwich if they have one.
没关系 我不需要吃东西
It's okay I don't eat.
总会有用得上的时候
You'll figure something.
保重 孩子
Take care,kid.
请挂断电话
Hang up the phone.
什么
Excuse me.
我有紧急情况
This is an emergency.
我不想伤害你
I don't wanna hurt you.
等一下 亲爱的
Hold on,hon.
当然可以 打我啊
Sure you do,hurt me.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我先打完这个电话
I'm gonna finish this call.
然后再来收拾你
Then I'm gonna stab you.
- 我认识你 - 我不觉得
- I know you - I don't think so.
Castiel
Castiel.
我们在天堂里见过
We've met in Heaven.
我叫Hael
My name was Hael.
你是个天使
You're an angel.
是吗
Am I.
没了翅膀还能叫天使吗
What's an angel without its wings.
嘿
Hey.
我就直接问了
I'm just gonna break the ice.
你是天使吗
Are you an angel.
有的时候人们希望我是
Sometimes they wish I were.
我叫Kim Schortz
My name is Kim Schortz.
我是医院里的默哀辅导员
I'm a grief counselor in this hospital.
是啊
Right,yeah.
抱歉 我有点儿累
Sorry,I'm just tired.
没有冒犯的意思 但是
All due respect,but.
我不会默哀的
I'm not grieving.
至少现在还没有
Not yet at least so.
恐怕不论面对现实有多困难
I'm afraid as hard as this may be.
现在正是时候
This might be a good time to talk.
面对不可抗力
About the inevitable.
我知道你是个好人 而且你是出于好意
I'm sure you're the nice person and that you mean well.
但是
But.
不可抗力
Inevitable.
我的世界里充满了反抗
That's a fighting world where I come from.
总有办法的
There's always a way.
而我是一个虔诚的信徒
And I'm a prayerful woman.
跟其他人一样相信奇迹
Who believes in miracles as much as the next.
但是我会看脑电图
But else I know how to read an EEG.
除非你还想告诉我
And unless you're telling me.
你还在等着天使
You have a direct line to those angel.
- 来帮你吗 - 对
- That you're looking for - Yeah.
不 我想没有了
No,I...guess I don't.
但是我有更好的
Bet I might have something better.
我后备箱里装着的可是地狱之王
I get the King of Hell in my trunk.
你的意思是
Is...is that.
不好意思 这是什么比喻吗
Sorry,is that a metaphor.
Crowley 你这个混蛋 听好了
Crowley,listen up,you son of a bitch.
敲一下肯定 两下否定
One for yes,two for no.
你还活着吗
You alive.
快点 别耍脾气了
Come on,don't be a pouter.
这就对了
Here we go.
是你祈祷了吗
You prayed.
是的 我需要帮助
Yeah,for help.
对 你还是先帮助我吧
Yes,you'll be helping me.
如果你对我撒谎的话 Dean Winchester
If you lie to me,Dean Winchester.
我会撕开你的喉咙的
I will rip your throat out.
Castiel在哪里
Where is Castiel.
是谁想知道
Who's asking.
每一个从家里被驱逐出来的天使都想
Try every angel that was ejected from their home.
好吧 这样的话 我就不知道了
Well,in that case,I have no clue.
放松点 兄弟
Easy there,brother.
这位年轻人祈祷的是我们的帮助
This young man has prayed for our assistance.
咱们是施以严酷
Are we creatures of wrath.
还是施以怜悯
Or compassion.
我赞成后者
I would argue the latter.
原谅我 兄弟
Forgive me,brother.
我没认出你是谁
I don't recognize you.
你放下武器之后 我很乐意和你重新认识一下
Happy to make you re-acquaintance,after you disarm.
这就是你对待
Come now,is that any way to treat.
在坠落中受伤的兄弟的方式吗
A brother injured in a fall.
你是谁
Who are you.
别在乎我
Never mind me.
你是Dean Winchester
You're Dean Winchester.
我听到你的祈祷了
I heard your prayer.
我是来帮助你的
And I am here to help.
好的
OK.
本来是很平常的一天
It was a normal day.
突然一切都
And then just.
黑了
Dark.
然后我就
And I was just.
开始坠落
Falling.
怎么会这样
How could that happen.
我不知道
I don't know.
你的荣光 都消失了
Your grace...it's gone.
但是我还能听见天使电台的内容
I do still hear angel radio,though.
这么说你听到他们了
Then you've heard them.
咱们的兄弟姐妹们
Our brothers and sisters.
都还在四处飘荡寻找皮囊
Many still circling for vessels.
他们中的很多都是
Most just.
那么无助
So afraid.
没有什么好怕的
There's nothing to be afraid of.
我可以向你保证
I can assure you.
但是在天堂 那里有秩序 那里有
But Heaven,there's order,there's.
目的
Purpose.
不管你信不信
Believe it or not.
人间有些东西比这些更有意义
There may be something even better down here.
我不明白
I don't understand.
这里为你
There's opportunity for you.
和其它坠落的天使提供了机会
The others who have fallen.
终于能做你喜欢的事情
To finally do what you like to do.
而不只是做你被安排的事情
Not just what you've been told.
那么我喜欢做什么
Then what would I like to do.
你来告诉我吧
Well,you tell me.
如果能随心所欲 你想做什么
If you could do anything,what would it be.
有一个地方
There's a place.
上次来人间的时候我建成了它
I built it when I was last here.
很多年前了
Many years ago.
一个很大的峡谷
A grand canyon.
大峡谷吗 对
The Grand Canyon,yes.
我想看看那里
I would like to see that.
那么 我们去看大峡谷吧
Let's go see the Grand Canyon,then.
你想帮我吗
You want to help.
先说你叫什么
Start with a name.
Ezekiel
Ezekiel.
好的 Ezekiel
All right,Ezekiel.
我怎么知道你不和其他天使一样
How do I know you're not hunting me.
在追杀我或者Castiel
Or Castiel like the other angels.
哦 我确定是有很多天使在追杀你们
Oh,I'm sure there are many angels who are.
而且数量很可能会越来越多
Many more on their way here,most likely.
你怎么知道
How do you know that.
你那样公开的祈祷
You put out an open prayer like that.
我那时实在很绝望
I must really be desperate.
不管你信不信
Believe it or not.
我们中的某些人仍然坚信我们的使命
Some of us still believe in our mission.
这意味着我们相信Castiel
That means we believe in Castiel.
和你
And you.
你说你坠落的时候受伤了
You said you were hurt during the fall.
是的
I was.
刚才和我兄弟扭打恶化了我的伤情
Entangling with my brother back there did me no favors.
但是我剩下的力量
But what strength I have left.
会全部用来帮助你
I offer to you.
我很想战斗 真的
I want to fight,I do.
但是我总感觉
But I just feel like.
感觉你没办法使劲
Like you got nothing to swing it out.
感觉你像在和影子打架
Like you're punching at shadows.
你要放弃战斗 挣扎
You gotta let go of fighting,scratching,and.
放弃求生
Looking for loopholes.
因为你没有出路了
Cause that ain't happening.
所以呢 我就这么死掉吗
So,what,I just die.
什么叫 就这么死掉
Just die.
你做了这么多好事
All the good you've done.
救了这么多人
All the people you've saved.
牺牲了这么多
All the sacrifices you've made.
你拯救了世界 孩子
You saved the world,son.
有多少人能这么说
How many people can say that.
有多少人能说自己的死
How many people can say that they have left this gut.
是为了
For the god for saken hunk of dirt.
让这个世界更美好
That much a better place.
你说你死了
What you call dying.
我把这称为功成名就 尘归尘 土归土
I call,leaving a legacy.
你还能治愈人吗
You're still able to cure things.
坠落之后
After the fall.
是的 我本应该可以 但是
Yes,I should be,but.
他太虚弱了
He's so weak.
谁
Who is this.
Dean
Dean.
Cass 发生什么了
Cass,what the hell is going on.
Metatron 他耍了我
Metatron,tricked me.
这不是天使试炼 是在驱逐天使
It wasn't angel trials.It was an spell.
我想告诉你一下
I wanted you to know that.
好的 但是我们现在有麻烦了
OK.That's great,but we've got ourselves a problem.
怎么了
What's wrong.
Sam 他 他快死了
Sam,he's,let's say he's dying.
怎么了
What happened.
不知道 一开始他很好 后来又不行了
Don't know.At first he was OK,and then he wasn't.
你听见我的祈祷了吗
Have you heard my prayers.
我向你祈祷了一晚上
I've been praying to you all night.
- Dean Metatron 他拿走了我的荣光 - 什么
- Dean,Metatron he,he took my grace - What.
别担心我了 你怎么救Sam
Don't worry about me.What are you doing for Sam.
竭尽我所能
Everything I can.
其实还有个天使在帮忙
There's actually another angel working on it right now.
什么天使
What other angel.
他叫Ezekiel 他很好
His name is Ezekiel.He's cool.
至少我觉得他很好
I mean I think he is.
Ezekiel
Ezekiel.
是的 他是个优秀的战士
Yes,he's a good soldier.
我到之前他应该能帮你
He should be able to help until I get there.
不 不 不 不能这样
No no no,that's not an option.
得等几天
Might be a few days.
Cass 听我说
Cass,listen to me.
有很多天使在外面
There are angels out there,okay.
他们在找你 而且他们很愤怒
They're looking for you and they're pissed.
不是所有天使都这样 Dean
Not all of them,Dean.
有一些只是在寻求指引
Some are just looking for direction.
有一些只是迷失
Some are just lost.
你在说什么
What are you talking about.
我遇见了一个
I've met one.
我想我能帮助她 Dean
I think I can help her,Dean.
不 Cass
No,Cass.
我知道你想帮忙 好吗
I know you wanna help,okay.
我知道 但是帮助天使
I do,but helping angel's.
本来就是让你陷入麻烦的原因
What got you in trouble in the first place.
我求你
Now I'm begging you.
就这么一次 照顾好你自己
For once look out for yourself.
直到我们弄清楚到底怎么回事
Until we figure out what the hell is going on.
别相信任何人
Trust nobody.
然后怎么样
And do what.
- 抛弃他们所有人 - 我靠 Cass
- Just abandon them all - Damn it Cass.
听听你在说什么
You hearing yourself.
现在是在战争中 而这是你的责任
There's a war on and it's on you.
成千上万的天使在
There's thousands of them out.
你说你失去了你的荣光 对吧
You said you'd lost your grace,right.
这就是说你是人类了
That means you're human.
这就是说你会流血 你要吃饭 要睡觉
That means you bleed and you eat and you sleep.
还有
And all the things you'd never.
所有你以前从来不用担心的一切
Had to worry about before.
我很好 Dean
I'm fine,Dean.
怎么了
What's going on.
我想有人来了
I think we got more company.
你先去基地
We'll get your ass to the bunker.
一个人去
Alone.
听到了吗
You hear me.
- Dean - 去吧 Cass
- Dean - Go!Cass.
Dean
Dean.
是天使吗
One of yours.
我正努力保住这具皮囊
I'm trying to secure the vessel.
我们应该离开
We need to move.
不 不 如果我们动他
No,no.If we move him.
他会死
He dies.
如果留下
If we stay.
那我们都会死
We could all die.
我不明白
I don't understand.
我和你一起去
I'll come with you.
我们可以一起去见你的朋友
We can see your friend together.
事情有点复杂
It's complicated.
可能会有麻烦
There could be trouble,it's.
最好还是我自己去
It's best if I go alone.
我的 我的朋友他
My...My friend he.
他需要我的帮助
He needs my help.
我需要帮助
I need help.
你能做到的 Hael
You can do this,Hael.
这是你的机会
This is your chance.
去帮助人们
To help people.
帮助自己
To help yourself.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
只要有这些
Long as these are up.
没有天使能进来
No angles are coming in.
你也出不去了
No one is coming out.
你觉得可以吗
You gonna okay with this.
我能接受
I'll manage.
怎么了
What.
他们来了
They are here.
好
Okay.
别为除了我以外的任何人开门
Do not open this door for anybody but me.
救他最重要
Save him.
听见了吗
You hear me.
所有人都出去 快
Everybody out,now.
都出去
Get out.
你能理解
You understand that.
我不能就这么让你走了
I couldn't just let you leave.
没了你我会迷失自己 Castiel
I'd be lost without you,Castiel.
是啊 我慢慢明白过来了
Yes,I'm beginning to see that.
把你留在我身边是我最小的要求了
It's the least I could ask of you.
考虑到
Considering...Well.
这都是你的错 不是吗
This is all your fault,isn't it.
让天使们坠落
Making the angels fall.
所以 我们开去大峡谷
So,we'll drive to the Grand Canyon.
你多给我讲讲人类的事
You'll tell me more about humans.
然后我会向你展示我的能力
And I'm gonna show you what I'm capable of.
我们会不只是朋友 Castiel
We'll going to become more than just friends,Castiel.
我们会成为一体
We are going to become one.
你想附在我身上
You want to possess me.
你的皮囊很强
Your vessel is strong.
我这个坚持不了多久了
This one won't hold me much longer.
你说得对 Castiel
You were right,Castiel.
我们在一起
With us together.
我可能会喜欢上这里
I think I could learn to like it here.
嘿 赶紧离开这儿
Hey,you got to get out of here.
快来
Come on.
待在我后面
Stay behind me.
或者不要
Or not.
这就是了
Here it is.
你要上路所需要的一切都在里面
Everything inside you need to help you on your way.
去吧孩子
Go on,son.
我会准备好几瓶冰啤酒等着你
I'll be waiting for you with a couple of cold ones.
对不起了
Sorry,old man.
Dean 你疯了吗
Dean,are you insane.
得了吧 Sammy
Come on Sammy.
Bobby是你想死的那部分
Bobby was the part of you did wants to die.
- 我知道很难受 但他必须离开 - 不
- I know it stings,but he had to go - No.
你必须离开
You have to go.
你什么时候才能意识到
When are you gonna realize.
已经结束了
It's over.
没有什么为之战斗的了
There is nothing to fight for.
不 你不相信这个
No,see,I know you don't believe that.
真的吗
Really.
你有什么计划 Dean
What's your plan,Dean.
我的计划
My plan.
我的计划是去抗争
My plan is to fight.
我的计划
My plan.
是去尝试
Is to try.
我的计划
My plan.
是去关心
Is to give a damn.
你告诉我什么都没有了
You are telling me that there is nothing.
你在告诉我没有什么可抗争了吗
You are telling me that there is nothing to fight for.
没有什么可希望了吗
That there is nothing to hope for.
不 我在告诉你 有的
No,I'm telling you there is.
你可能不喜欢
You might not like it.
你可能不接受
You might not accept it.
但是确实有 在那个房子里
But it's in there.It's in that house.
你知道房子里是什么
You know what's in that house.
如果你自己都不愿意
Now I can't help you.
那我也帮不了你
If you ain't not willing to fight for yourself.
我知道
I know.
没事的
It's okay.
这是我想要的
It's what I want.
简单的说吧
Let me make this easy.
告诉我Castiel在哪
Tell me where Castiel is.
不然你弟弟会生不如死
Or your brother is gonna wish he were dead.
有本事自己过去啊
Good luck getting past the warding.
我们会的
But we will.
我们过去之后 我会剥了他的皮
And when we do.I'm gonna strip off all his skin.
让你看着
And you are gonna watch.
去死吧
Bite me.
有没有人告诉过你
Anybody ever told you.
你打人像天使一样没劲
You hit like an angle.
你好 Sam
Hello,Sam.
我一直在等你
I've been waiting for you.
好的,等一下
OK,wait,wait,wait,wait.
我会告诉你Cass在哪儿
I will tell you where Cass is.
我只是有一个问题
I just have one question.
问
Ask.
如果天堂被锁上了
If Heaven is locked.
那么我做这个 你们会去哪儿
Where will you go when I do this.
发生了什么
What the hell is happening.
警报突然就响起来了
This just started.
还有这些反天使标记
And the warding.
我恐怕我比我想象中的更虚弱
I'm afraid I'm weaker than I thought.
我很抱歉 Dean
I am sorry,Dean.
不不不
No,no,no.
我们有过协议
We had a deal,okay.
我掩护你救Sam
I fight,you save.
我现在没那个能力了
And would that I could.
恐怕现在太迟了
I'm just afraid it's too late.
开什么玩笑
Are you kidding me.
你是说没有办法来救我弟弟的命
You're saying there is no way to save my brother's life.
我恐怕没有好的方法了
No good ways I'm afraid.
那坏的方法呢
What are the bad ones.
现在我们还有的选择 不论好坏
We get options here,man,good or bad.
让我听听你的想法
Let me hear you.
我不敢保证
I cannot promise.
但是有个我能拯救你弟弟的机会
But there is a chance I can fix your brother.
用我体内的荣光
From me inside.
你体内
From inside.
你要怎么做
So what.
你要把他开个大洞吗
You gonna open him up.
附身
What,possession.
你想附身Sam
You want to possess Sam.
我告诉过你
I told you.
没门
No way.
你要明白 是你需要帮助
Understood,It's your call.
不 是Sam需要帮助
No,it's Sam's call.
但是Sam是绝对不会同意
There's no way in hell he'd say yes.
自己被任何东西附身的
To being possess by anything.
他宁愿死
He would rather die.
那我就不打扰你们了
I'll leave you two alone.
等等
Wait.
如果我考虑这件事 我的意思是只是考虑
If I consider this,I mean just consider it.
我需要一些东西
I need something,man.
你必须证明给我他现在到底有多糟
You get to prove me how bad he is.
闭上你的眼睛
Close your eyes.
我得承认 在我听说是你要来的时候
I must admit it when I heard it was you.
我觉得有必要亲自跑一趟
Well I had to come myself.
我猜这件事情会使你得到愉悦
I bet you get off on this.
也许吧
Perhaps.
但不是你想象的那样
But not in the way you assume.
来接手像Sam Winchester这样的人
I consider it to be quite the honor.
是我的荣幸
To be collecting the likes of Sam Winchester.
我一向尽量避免通过类似的审判
I tried so hard not to pass judgment at times like this.
不合我的口味
Not my bag,you see.
不过你
But you.
干得不错 我的孩子
Well played,my boy.
我需要知道一件事
I need to know one thing.
什么事
Yes.
如果我跟你走
If I go with you.
你能保证
Can you promise.
这次就是最后的终结了吗
That this time it will be final.
如果我死了
That if I'm dead.
我就是死了
I stay dead.
没人能转化我 没人能用交易救活我
Nobody can reverse,nobody can deal it a way.
没人会因我而受到伤害
And nobody else get hurt because of me.
我能承诺
I can promise that.
你他妈在干什么 Sam
What the hell are you doing,Sam.
就像你看到的 已经没剩多少时间了
As you can see,there's not much time.
我知道
I know.
妈的 我知道
Damn it I know.
附身之后会怎么样
How will it work.
大家互惠互利
Mutual benefit I suppose.
我可以在治愈Sam的同时为自己养伤
I heal Sam when I'm healing myself.
那等到他复原的时候呢
And when he's healed.
我就离开
I leave.
这是目前最好的情况了 Dean
It's the best of the bad situation,Dean.
就算我同意了
Even if I said yes.
那也不意味着你能霸占他的身体
It doesn't means squat.
Sam永远也不会同意的 对你不会
Sam would never say yes,not to you.
但他不会拒绝你的
But he would say yes to you.
我不想伤害你
I don't want to hurt you.
我本不想伤害任何天使
I didn't want to hurt any of them.
我想帮你们
I want to help you.
我会奉献我的一生来帮助你们所有人
I will devote my life to helping you all.
你知道你的话听起来有多可笑吗
Do you know how ridiculous you sound.
在你做过那样的事请之后 还想帮助天使
Help angels?After what you did.
他们不需要你的帮助 Castiel
They don't want your help,Castiel.
你们要你死
They want your head.
你错了 我也是你们中的一员
You're wrong,I'm one of you.
我永远都是你们中的一员
I will never stop being one of you.
你还不明白吗
Don't you get it.
在一起的话 我能保护你 Castiel
Together,I can protect you,Castiel.
我不需要你
I don't need you.
我也不需要你的保护
And I don't want your protection.
如果你就这么把我留在这个破皮囊里
If you leave me here in this broken girl.
我发誓 Castiel
I swear,Castiel.
我会告诉他们你在哪
I will tell them where you are.
然后他们会追杀你
And they will hunt you.
直到最后一口气
Until their last breath.
他们都会找那个
They will seek revenge on the angle.
毁灭天堂的天使报仇的
That did this who destroyed heaven.
闭嘴
Stop.
他们会找你报仇
They'll seek a vengeance.
跟这次的情况相比
On you that will make god striking down.
当年上帝驱逐Lucifer看起来像小儿科
Lucifer seemed like child's play.
你可以别说了吗
Stop it.
我会告诉所有天使
I will go on angel radio and tell them.
你的所作所为 除非你接受我
Everything unless you open your heart.
接受我吧
Say yes.
是时候了Sam
It's time,Sam.
走吧
Shall we.
等等
Hold on.
- Dean - 没事 Sam
- Dean - It's okay,Sam.
我
I.
我本来想带月形面包圈 但是
Would brought cronuts but.
时间有限 你懂的
Time's short so.
- 确实 - 发生了什么
- By all means - What's going on.
- 我找到办法了 - 太迟了
- I found a plan - It's too late.
我跟他走
I'm going.
不 不 不 不
No,no,no,no,no.
- 听我说 - 你确实是在这里吗
- Listen to me - Are you even here.
我不会再为此挣扎了
I'm not fighting this anymore.
你必须挺过去
You have to fight this.
我能解决
I can fix this.
但是你不能拒绝我
Okay,but not if you shut me out.
还不到时间
It's not his time.
多少时间是由Sam决定
That's for Sam to decide.
现在 听我说 Sam
Now,Sam,listen to me.
我承诺过
I made you a promise.
你和我 在那个教堂
In that church.You and me.
不论面对什么
Come whatever.
靠 不就是说现在
Hell if this ain't whatever.
你必须让我进去 兄弟
But you got to let me in,man.
你得让我来帮助你
You got to let me help.
如果没有你 我活着还有什么意义
There ain't no me if there ain't no you.
我该怎么做
What do I do.
你同意了是吗
Is that a yes.
是的
Yes.
好
Come on.
你是谁
Who are you.
到底发生了什么
What the hell is going on here.
我也不知道
I have no idea.
所以
So.
你进去的时候是什么情况
How's the looking there.
不太好
Not good.
让他痊愈得花费一番功夫
There's much work need to be done.
他会醒过来的 是吗
I mean he's gonna wake up,right.
会的
He will.
那么 他会
So,what he does.
他会感觉到你的存在吗
What,is he gonna feel you inside.
会默默数伤口吗
Triaging his spleen.
他感觉不到我的
He will not feel me,no.
Sam不需要知道
There's no reason for Sam.
我在他体内
To know I'm in here at all.
你开玩笑吗 不 这明明
You're joking?No.This is.
这是一件大事啊
This is too big.
如果你告诉他
And what will he do.
他被天使附身 他会怎么做
If you do tell him he's possessed by an angel.
好吧 他能理解的
Well,he'll have to understand.
如果他不能呢
And if he does not.
没有他的允许
Without his acceptance.
Sam随时随地都能驱逐我
Sam can eject me,at any time.
特别是在我很虚弱的时候
Especially with me so weak.
如果Sam不让我待下去
And if Sam does eject me.
他就会死
He will die.
那我们从现在就开始保密
Then we'll keep the secret for now.
或者等到Sam能够适应的时候
Or until Sam's well enough that he.
等他不需要天使代步器的时候
Doesn't need angelic pacemaker.
或者我想办法告诉他 我
Or I'll find a way to tell him.I...I.
听着 现在就相当于他住院了
Listen,as for him,being in hospital.
我必须找到解决的方法
I have to figure something out.
如果你愿意 我可以清除他所有的记忆
I can erase that all if you like.
他什么都不会知道
He will not remember any of this.
我们在哪儿
Where are we.
Sam
Sam.
怎么了
What.
没事 放轻松
Okay,take it easy.
你现在感觉怎么样
How you're,how you're feeling.
很不舒服
It's hurt.
感觉像睡了一周一样
Like I'm slept for a week.
睡了一天还差不多
Try a day.
你从天使坠天开始一直睡到现在
But out since the sky was spittin' angels.
到底发生了什么
What the hell happen.
你还记得什么
What do you remember.
教堂在摇晃
The church is feeling like crap.
天使在坠落
The angels falling.
就这些
And that's it.
但是你没有难受的感觉
But you're feeling good.
是的 我 我就是
Yeah,I mean I just.
我在副驾驶上晕了一天
You've been driving around with me passed out.
你也就开了一天的车吗
On the passenger seat for a day.
我也停过啊
I mean I stopped,you know.
跟一群日本游客照照相什么的
Let a few Japanese tourists take some pictures.
没人吃我豆腐
Nobody gets too handy.
我知道你会挺过来
I know you'd pull through.
在教堂里说的那些话 我是认真的
I meant what I said at church.
以你的能力 干什么都可以
You're capable of anything,Sam.
我要是错了 也没机会跟你说这话
Hell,if you didn't prove me right.
好
Good.
我们还有活要干
'Cause we got work to do